[Music]
and
m
[Music]
or not [Music]
no [Music
]
m
e
[Music]
now not if I am a man
turrion
[Music] you tell me
that your life follows its ebb and flow that you don't
think when you act that's not it I
'm looking for someone else at the time of
watering
not
well
[Music] I
will resist
your love
arriving as always the passion if
you knew what I feel no no we
started
[Music]
I felt thank you very much
ah
no
[Music]
the moon fell
if I yes no don't
tell me that your life
[Music]
free
e don't you think when you finish or is it not
Pérez directing someone else to be
able to hit
[Music]
I couldn't in love
dt
[Music]
a broth
[Music] I
could raise the game of your love  to gifts
as always the passion you want what I feel would
n't be my love
[Music]
yes yes
a warmth
all
the fire of your love
[Music] I'm
sorry
edition
[Music] I
have many thanks
all my love all my love for you
oh my life
[Applause]
someone wants to be the mandala
yes yes
of everything
in itself
d
[Music]
come on
milk
[Music]
and I don't yes
in itself you
know
yes
here yes yes
and yes s in
itself
[Music]
yes yes yes
in itself
and that's the part of the
teacher training of the school amounts
between as you can't hear it a friend
in his new song I'll change that
vertex and everyone is welcome to
become a teacher of that variety
world where but they have to do all
the work
and if he's been doing it for 27 years he says he's been doing it for
like 10 or 12 years
with the nonchalance
with Iverson and giving an authentic 20 years
to his story
and he's 32 and he's older than
many of you
ah
d
we had very days  Very beautiful times, and
also difficult times.
Every time you do big projects, big
things, big
problems, you also have big
problems. When you're in my new light, that's when they realize
this. They
have a choice. They can't
decide not to do big things
or to do big things and work with the
big problems that come with it.
Huila is this
windy thing. What I realized is
that we need a binary jaguars, which
is binary. It's a rulebook that
left me behind. We don't have
a paradisiacal zone anymore. We don't
have much anymore either.
Everything disappeared, and paradise,
cool. Why
am I addicted to translating coffee?
Full Idrac, leaving German paperwork. It's
difficult for me to have time to create
all these rules, and I'm always
avoiding it. I don't know why.
Gates time,
we must have certain rules, regulations,
and written regulations are always
better than unwritten ones
because
everyone can read them and follow them.
So I wrote a rulebook for
this week.
[Music]
In the last training session on amounts,
we made a rule about birds
and bees, which is a rulebook.  Sexuality
for teachers
and I was ashamed to talk about it, he explains in
Afghanistan, but it's funny sometimes
and that's a little more exciting, but
now for the boring stuff.
These rules were written by the entire
management of S
Rating, whom we have to thank.
This week the topic to talk about is
financial policies, which is a spacey
point, which is especially boring. Let's
start
for the egg-free day. At least
we're going to have clarity.
Javi Dominguez, I
have a 12-page document, ago 10
dyn swipe inning, and I'm going to give you 3
pages per night.
Here are the first three pages of
the story,
and I start by talking about the
regulations that my teacher Zubin
Mehta Martinière gave me when I met my
teacher. From the first day,
I took a class with him.
As I mentioned, the Dalai Lama
told me that I should go with the
teacher, Elda Huanchumay, and I went to his room, and
Mary Ann Salmon and they say, "Let's go, they're a
sad thing, like
a little hamburger in the
national dish of Tibet,
Perez with spinach, because..."  I'm a
vegetarian
[Music]
It was meeting him
and I thought I'm going to impress him. The entourage
isn't there because he's been learning for a few months. They'll be in
bloom. They install Eastwood and better
sit down. I was centering the floor on
his bed in the software and well, he asked me
what I want in this San Diego and I
said Nathan, who comments water and water and
damn, what does it mean to be pure
[Music]
the two
Leroys and take
look and then he told me that he threw them away
immediately. There are the ones that
lately, then I said I would like to
ask you to be my teacher
at Jamie Paintball and I gave him my checkbook.
What is this?
This is all my money and he gave me Mani, your
money,
but I've done better with it.
The Guadiana, play for drama, is that you're going to
pay for the aroma. Amin Azmani, that
enough money in the case of Snow
Price is priceless,
priceless. This Sunday the lady, no
insults, alarm, neutral images
because the weapon is priceless. There would be no
money,
nobody has enough money to pay.
From the strong origin, he taught me for 30 years, he
is a voluntary slave
and my friends told me this guru
is taking advantage of you.  I'm doing, I'm taking
advantage of yesterday, today is the 10th, and Martín
Labbé, all his dishes and all his clothes, I
manage for him, they have to
verify in that position of his
garden, absent, a thousand things,
and you,
and he taught me several hours a day,
Gilabert Church Minitti, he never charged me
anything, strong shine, for 30 years,
I throw this checkbook
at the monastery,
if they accept you at the monastery,
and the teachers who have been there longer
teach the new ones, in this it's free, it's about
paying someone, something strange, they
might even be offended,
and it doesn't mean that I don't help him, in fact,
I gave a lot of money for the monastery,
for the
name, it's my way, and nobody asked me to, I
'm a story, I said when I started,
and I felt that I thought we shouldn't
charge the artist because it's an honor, in a
sign of arms,
in this way I don't think the teachers
should be paid, I
think we shouldn't charge for it,
from the action plan, well, being
online, for example, all 18 foundation courses
are also online, try it, from
Infonavit, you can download them for free,
and you can also do whatever you
want,
and this team,
Mohamed Nidal, we usually tell each other how many
We had downloads, not being tempted
with so many thousands that we stopped
and we don't charge for these materials.
Examined in sparks, there are thousands. It
takes like 12 to 15 years of hard work.
Javier, one night and training, the next
class. The best of one night is
translating the next class in the
classroom. My sister, I
yelled at her, "Tell
them to turn off the light!" They were in the
next room.
The light is bothering me. The sun is the sunrise. What a fork!
[Laughter]
We worked all night.
It seems like
the IFE and it should be free.
Bar,
there are some things that you can charge for
[Music]
and there are things that you
can ask for donations for, even for
yourself.
What are the regulations?
And we're also going to put it online.
Sword, what can you charge for?
What can't you charge for?
What levels? Telehit Ford? And what kind
of things can you ask for donations for?
And is it valid to ask for donations for your
personal costs? But we're going to talk
about that
too. How do we ask? It's very important
in Phoenix 2. In one night, I'm going to
finish this in one night
to take  like three nights for it to
work
and it's being at the mercy of yesterday
here's a list of expenses for
which, if required, estimates
coronation light is beach like this
retreat for example
and they weren't
if we didn't charge for the hotel or the
rooms nobody has the money to be
able to cover this
number one on the list
and your wisdom goes up 100 percent I do
n't know what happened since in
typical training so I tell you keep your
commitments
Merino if you're married and settled
love each other and if you have a family Smackdown is
n't dharma I had bots to
cause you problems that you have to eat men
city in and mind and the commitments you
already have are titles that keep me
those commitments states to a lady to
make me mind of the champion and it's not
giving more to make a commitment to your
company understood 10 of Pierre's endurance
of Zeeuw and pick and your heart fun
with M&T you disappear a couple of ideas a
week because you have
spiritual commitments your heart team
you have to keep your previous promises
before making new promises
if you need more time
you have to negotiate your commitments are
old from a  honorable form with
honor and the title has components that have to
do with company detective wife in your
wife or husband in the heart the wii and it
have to agree in toughness in Buddhism
is a type stand by the world a
family's money is 50% the husband's 50% the
husband's in finances of this city council
had financial decisions are made
together the benefit of queens house
poultry fest
we are in a beautiful house of a
digital university teacher in the
meeting time in wake last and he gave us a
very important class on the path of
demand if there is endurance of the language and he
said I want to give you my house
in internet word continues and he came these
leaves with a cardboard suitcase and Karina
Flores who couldn't buy an
equal way of hardware back was a
road box with a rope in up the
ladies night gives classes in medicine and
this lady said this class is a lover
of my marriage I
want to give you my house which is worth 3
million homes to west behind and I
was behind her in Hawaii
he is saying in Islay
and my teacher I
think you
said be
this too
with this money
[Music]
and driving home that is driving very
quietly
no  I could resist
and I told her what we can do with these
crazy ones
and if she doesn't continue the be great and the best no
she's going to regret it
later yes yes slater she's going to have
doubts about this initiative of the
greens of a nation that special tag and he
said he doubts about a donation
made is a very special day bad how many how many
100 dollar bills he
gave at start and he starts to get angry
then it's very bad karma it's
especially bad do
n't let a sponsor give you
too much and faithful to be if you're not
sure
tell them to wait
also owe 6 mans gives less in six
months in itself
[Music]
if you sign a contract for a building
or something so for this don't put the name
of wii
the certificates as as teachers is
the only external
the sion is karma in the fulham and it's
beautiful in everything seen
efe and don't be afraid that I had the
baby
do it in a responsible way said
welch santander of talking about peanuts and
nate big families have 7 wongs and
sell  Doubly before renting a
place, have the money in advance from
your students, and if they don't
have it, don't rent it anywhere.
Don't rent it expecting the
money to come in on the day; it's a bad
idea to have them change your
commitments in January during the Monegros Armani neighborhood,
and then rent it. People used to come in on
time.
If you get into trouble,
be responsible and don't take risks.
Biguá Whitman and be wise with
money. And no one in this ministry,
in English and in Spanish, says that
money is the root of all evil,
with the word "hello" as the subject of the root.
Hello,
hello,
come
before they understand
all this.
[Music]
More costs than we can
charge,
and this is something we can and should
charge. It's equally clear if you want to
come to the class in a city, in a
civic way, salsa in Juniors for free,
with the accents, find, and if you have
money, that it's not a big house and you
can pay for it, go ahead. Wireless connection,
25 mind, team, keep duplex,
wysiwyg, north shopping, Trinidad,
make sure your partner agrees
with people coming twice a
week and that they believe  in a disaster that they're not going to
clean up, destination,
I have this thing that I hate, the facts,
we're in a beautiful house of a
university professor, manager, in the
meeting time, in weight last, and he gave us
a very important class on the path of
calling 'crisis,' the endurance of languages, and he
told me, 'I want to give you my house
in the internet word, if he came, these sheets
with a cardboard suitcase, leans strong,
and that they couldn't buy it, an
equal way of hardware back, it was a
road box with a rope, in up the
ladies night, he gives classes in medicine, and
this lady said, 'This class, lover of my
marriage, I
want to give you my house that's worth 3
million yen,' water behind, and I
was behind her in Hawaii,
he's saying in Islay,
and my teacher, I think you said, '
Be here,
this team is also that, the grass
with this money
[Music]
and managing house, that this manages her very
quietly,
resist,
and I told her what we can do with
these three crazy ones,
and this doesn't follow the mustache, and the best one, no,
she's going to regret it
after following up, down later, she's going to
have doubts about this initiative
of the Werder Nation, and her special is here,' she
said  Doubting a donation
made is especially
Arizona how many how many
$100 bills
gave start
is a very bad weapon especially bad do
n't let a sponsor give you
too much and faithful to be if you are not
sure what they say to wait
also has six men of six months
the signature is a contract for a building
or something so precious put the name of
100 we be easy of you
the certificates as as teachers is
the only
external
that is your karma and it is beautiful in two
combis davis
efe and not that you are afraid that I had the
ventura pons but do it in a
responsible way and it was the Santander has next to
the peanut and nit of sant just your
entertainment of the doubly before
renting a place have the money in
advance from your students if you do
n't have it don't rent it then
they kept young cheer up don't rent it
hoping that the money will come to give the
day is a bad idea to be changed
first when blacks armani the
commitments of January during and after
the rent people want kid on time
james in windermere and  Ford
problems
be responsible and don't take
equal risks Whitman and be wise with
money in English
Manny is alive
in English and in Spanish they say that
money is the root of all evil with the
word of Zhanhe everything at the root
hello hello
come
before you understand
we are next to the costs that we are
that we can charge
and this is something that we can must
charge stimulant with keys if you want to
come to the class in a city way and
Havana
in juniors for free with the cities
find and if you have money you have a
big house and you can pay for it go ahead
connection hours 25 mind type more in gap
topless week end of helping your clinic
to make sure that your partner is
okay with people coming twice a
week and this believes in a disaster that they do
n't clean up
I have this thing that I hate the facts
Vitoria for desktop
that apnea
let's start time
is time for total confusion
[Music]
very strange people
who like to get confused
[Music]
we are covering the questions and
answers of the homework
and one of political reflection was in the
definition ballot cut
week the desire tutiven to achieve
enlightenment  from a wedding
to help all the people in the
Disney universe and if definition is the
easy definition may stain
star shape in thongs love complicate the
blood has a more complicated definition
before Carlos Marx
unfortunately the people who
wrote these tasks 25 years ago
video the complicated definition I
also have to give
[Music]
let's start Ixtlán is long
pipe today I'm going to give you point by point
this mail moment awareness is one
and my main mental consciousness
Jaime consciousness in primary mental main
and
in the wire way the highest path of
the great path that wants to
achieve total enlightenment
for the benefit of all
he is more can be mister mine
and this and
which raised with the same mental state
and the desire to achieve this enlightenment
in the sector and is the door
to enter the path the great path
have more
and of the great division of all the
teachings in queens
between points of view and activities and it
is an activity in reading do
n't worry and if I had written the
task I would
never have put this
this person is probably trying
to impress their students
[Music]
nothing
when we studied this in the
monasteries of as a
young monk of  TyC Sports takes every
part of the definition in
Washington, they say why this is there and
they call it "Night with." Usually it's
a negative reason, and I was able to
sell it. Anyway, if we don't put this in, there's going to
be confusion about big, where
Victor is, so much definition. We're going to take
the big parts of this definition from
Google, it's cool,
and we're going to talk about why it should be
there. It's
always going to be something negative, and Kingdom
Tower in the definition of coups, in the
sense that if you don't put this in a
definition, there's going to be a problem.
Sandwiches, no.
7,
and something that isn't pretty is going to
become political because you took
that out of the definition. I'm sorry for
that question.
Your problem is all
classic. I already told you, all the bad things in this
class come from you. Nothing. This
video of normals, this is very important
in the monastery on YouTube. By saying,
when we talk about SS visit,
main line increasing, then we say
that the main mind, and not a
mental function, is my mind mention ice.
Here we go,
Mahajan, go see the path, the great
path
of moment among clouds. At the moment
we enter the great path, this moment
the river is at the moment  The one we have
can take away real if we say that this
person is on the great path
Maritza this this rhythm me the same as
saying that he has in Wichita
his wei wei wei Inditex Phoenix and why is it that we
have to put the great path
in the definition of casters baby x 7
because there are little baby balls that are not
the pretty ones
thank you the little baby balls will make noise
power that are not the real little bag here
[Music]
has a special name you know already know
what about
sugarcane
when it's snowing and you should learn
about sugarcane in India,
study India after, like there are poor people
in Hummer who have these roads without
and have a lot of hands to
grind this sugarcane, these sugarcanes,
by default,
walk
and follow the trucks that are from
the sugarcane plantations
and pieces of sugarcane
and take these sugarcanes and
put them in their cart in Benidorm and
Taiwan, class
news if you ask them for a glass of
sugarcane juice, old big sugarcane
and they grind it and give it to you  Dan
is incredibly dirty, Guanta Mandrin,
with once I took one at the Crostis and
crossed the street, there's someone who doesn't know
anyone, they just win things, I took it
cross and cross in the street,
from the PP there's an old debate, okay, bye bye bye,
West Eminem, Fire
Wind, it's an internal wind,
for example, when all the paintings
move towards the tourist and push towards
Vanessa Davies, when you have a baby it
attaches and pushes down, Winspear,
when you spit,
the plan to cooperate and pushes it, the
minister goes, when you vomit out by the whole
valley,
a big philosophical question comes up,
yes,
yes, all the other various contribute and
push the vomit,
the valley of diarrhea
is that all the, going being the tourist, come
together and push down on top,
in theory that's not possible
in Jerez, addicted, I've injured myself
vomiting from having diarrhea at the same time
[Music]
but I did it
although
and then wants it is possible
because we're talking about this, what
he does
with sugarcane
[Music]
and there are many that are still not the
real one,
it's called a little bottle of sugarcane  sugar
in the min
[Music]
and it means that the children followed this
truck with them, they stole them until they were chewed up
From the first test index, who in the
test
because there's a little bit of
flavor in the skin and in the bamboo
insa and it takes about 10 minutes to get to the
center and we call it the meat.
There's something we call a sugarcane ball
by Tim Clark and this means that today you
're close to the tree. If you had to go and
not 30 starter, you're trying to
get what was the field,
for example. You haven't seen all
the beings in the universe yet.
Today, they have never had an emotional target.
Also, you haven't had
the real emotion of wanting to save all
the beings in the universe yet.
You're progressing. We
call this a lot of people in the
class, and Robert Barista, you hear that I'm going
to record them and they have to listen to each other
about HBO, The Cheetah with My Team,
watching politics. You'd like to
develop, Bayern Munich, Mark Webber,
but you're not there yet. We
call this a
sugarcane ball.
I'm hard way, eternal,
so we must say the great way. The
definition of the International Board,
up there were, because in the definition of
the little bottle, it should have the real one
and only those who have the  real may
be in this I'm
not
going to share something deeper that I just
had that I hadn't seen in
25 years
there are two parts to this strange sugar
[Music]
there are two types of
sugarcane bag one is the skin and the other the tube
that fits well here
yes let's
call the sugarcane skin the
swing love is sweet not much the future
andrés have the stick and without biting the
stick
on this plane inside time and if
you get to the inside
then inside inside that's the
real
but when you're just sitting in class
your first class your first class at the
bowling alley there are
no teeth and talking about
bags you have no idea what they're
talking about it's sad but you
start to get interested jazz telecom
technically that's what we call the
sugarcane skin bottle in class finn jr and when you've been
coming to class in Guadalajara for
several years and a favorite hormone male
and you learn a lot about body
chita perez don't complete
scare and immigratory spinning with
this complete spontaneous feeling
inside  You, I'm working in your clothes,
Bayern, don't stop, you're already working on
it and it's close but you're not there yet,
you have Kutcher
in this feeling, we call it that
each part, James,
who the three parts of the account,
the sugarcane in the skin,
welcome, some classes, kind of
Tarquini, it's going to update and people
talk about voice, also it sounds attractive, you do
n't know exactly what it's about,
well, and Camps are signing goods, then you
come for a few months when this tree
by I sat and you understand more about the
wizards
of the tube
and finally it comes, salt
inside me to the flesh of
the sugarcane,
that's cold, by grace it's the real little bag
when you get to the skin, the flesh
inside
is when we call it
chewing on the outside, still we
Mahayana
tomorrow, so that's why
the great path in the
definition,
this is something that bothers me quite a bit and it's
worth 100 dollars,
everything is measured in Manhattan and suddenly
the rest of the tired
Sam Jackson of the table tell me without a doubt
perfect in everything, in the perfect and total,
the lighting,
Samia Collins also means
professional and all saints,
the second means  Total
enlightenment,
firstly, I'm very attracted to this
word. I love
this medal, the
water from yesterday, it
also irritates me at the same time, but
everything in life in history and for women, what a
refresher of total enlightenment.
[Music] Were there
people who reached
total enlightenment but don't have fingers or
something like that, and it usually avoids me a lot? This
is enlightenment, no, it isn't, which
means the least I've given for a
hundred, being them for the region,
don't be
sure of much,
total is because it's wheat board and
chita the line
because we know it's not what would be
chita isn't urbana trans, why we say bull,
total means that it's like a joke
because if it's not 50, it's
barely 50, it
's my sister in this case, Nirvana and
enlightenment are not different things and
nothing in a white the heart similar sing
in a similar way.
[Music]
To the two of them, to stop the suffering, the
two, the two sisters,
Ignacio, separated the suffering
and the two are now free from suffering,
but the bus stop software, but in
shorter enlightenment, to help all
beings that are in my teacher for a
better answer, let's
go, almost 50 dollars,
also that trying
is  dangerous because for the less rich path
[Music]
because for the lesser path china yan al
nirvana is enlightenment stung by the
lower way indiana nirvana disco in light
in
I want more information about what you
call the lower path
anyone can see it for free high
of baseball scam very good condition
except except word either just gray
shut up
although the club
tracks usually gives a clue the
different paths
[Laughter]
no
one has a little arrow and the other doesn't juanjo
bowling you hold on jones
what we're missing
ah
in them not only five of this art
that christie's
insomnia that leads you think it breathes
real food
why they don't leave you can save the
living wings on the path gymnastics don't
think it can save all the bucks
I want to hear about the different
paths
jackson how many paths and 3
those are all of which are
of the listeners
the highest of the buddhists also
each one has five paths of ink
all and in total there are 15 so 15
paths that
but the definition already said of the fact
understand
is also a redundancy
Yes it is,
and each path is
different.
What's the difference? In fact, many
times they coincide with the master laser
type mini type.
Low, medium, and high practitioners are
willing to see
those with low motivation only in person,
which was
low growth. The team, I do
n't know what strange thing it is, make money.
People in the middle
want to free themselves from samsara, and the high ones, those with
high motivation, who want to become enlightened.
It's a technique.
People on these three different
paths
boast, verify, because on path 5 they
call it path 5.
That's all, Sanders,
noticing, change, am in everything. So that's why
we must say a
total enlightenment in Bern, Torrent, Sax
of Honor.
In fact, the enlightenments that are not
total, that is,
the people who are looking for
nirvana, can set sail for themselves.
They call it having good
MCD enlightenment, and for them it's already the
end, the end.
But when you arrive and the ends don't have it,
in fact, you realize that it's not the end.
This week I wake up, there are still
three types of enlightenment
for listeners. Fernet,
cars, it's just urban,
and there's Magellan's enlightenment.
What is this?
Okay, it moves
away from that fact, that's why it must
be total in the definition,
how
cool
[Music]
because it is our definition of saying
for others
there is some enlightenment, is it not
for others there are
two paths, the same joke,
good news for you, infinite
this great month, you already finished that silly task
number three
[Applause]
and now you can start the stupid task
number 4, you were supposed to
finish 4
but we're not going to do it,
but let's try, index, know,
fan of the mountain range, this is a
very fun division of volleyball, Cheetah
Wheelies, the end,
news
at level 8, Delight
Binner, look at leadership,
okay,
we use for level 8, it says
in purity in Buddhism, whispers, and the one
who should not be identified,
you can also divide bowling into three
types, the war crimes intervene, and
tomorrow we're going to talk about the four
types, date night, they identify them, for
tonight we talk about 3,
first of kings, for the first is the
bowling of a king
[Music]
and it is that he wants to enlighten your first in
light,
free leaders towards other people to
the  illumination in the mind
the way you think of
illumination to someone I'm
going to enlighten myself first I'm going to
bring all the people with me
senti time saints the item and origin
and also origin sometimes it's called the
joke of eating the meat
this is a question 100 dollars perhaps
Arocha
not confirm it well 100 dollars to
Nisman and I need money
because it's called little bottle of how of the
meat
in the synapse
the cooking Théophile
sure
already ready in the 100 dollars
there's a family that's relaxing in the
mountains
[Music]
I think the dad
to feed us a little more and then he
thinks
if I eat this animal
in the mail I can last for a week
for example and be able to ask for help
and he does it
survives for a week and receives help
and this is the eat the meat joke of
how the meat
[Applause]
of the K
Moscato I
rescue
my friend I am your friend
more cat searched
more menu
the restaurant which goes twice a
week
ok
and arts
no no no
Kim
the barrel of WTI concentrate  First
in their understanding of illumination
and they bring it to other people. The
illumination is a second type.
They are called shepherds.
In
the one, there have been golfers, and they
want other people to go before
entering the city,
and they are pushing the sheep to go to
the front of a new place. And they are nobles of that
water, and without me, I'm going to wait. Wolfers, I had
water first.
I'm going to help you. The first one I do is mouth-to-
mouth, and I'm going to come after this. They are
the best. I'm going to save. Right, no,
this goal is a myth. It's natural. It's not
correct. Okay, and city shadows of age
where they hear you say it or
tell them they are crazy. Pay and pay.
[Music]
Because it's that you're crazy.
Hamas is a good idea. Your delay and
online were several. The one who delays their
illumination for other people
is the only way to help other
people is by enlightening Caesar.
Also for this condition,
flour tortilla, correct, is traditional. It's
traditional. He pointed out this way, but it
's not correct. He didn't see it because of the scam. Wendy
Leigh, day and night, mind the kind of
things of the moment. Properly, PM of today
in Paris of the PP
illumination.  Because when it comes to enlightenment,
thousands of bodies can be demanded. I have a
dilemma in mind: I'm going to delay my
enlightenment so I do
n't have a thousand bodies, and
the decision doesn't make sense. He said there's a
tradition given by the
death scam that there was some way he would be
willing to do it if it would work, since it was,
and that's the point.
And in case it would help people,
Agustín, if I would be left in hell
while you go to the enlightenment of the
orchard, but it doesn't work that way. Also, the
interest of Angel Cappa, of a dad type, in
how much you want, are you willing to go to
hell to help other people
who would get out of hell? You have fame,
they lean towards code, and a famous example
called now in our acute and the
bowling chip of Engel, he jokingly
reached the hells,
he was pulling a cart with another
person
and he was the guard, the guard of the you with
me is giving them whippings,
give it to me, practitioner,
and the guard of the game hells
that is fine and whipped him
at that moment the man died
and immediately,
higher birth and continue working
here
near the 18 courses of the path of the so-
called Itokawa, it took me a lot  time at
what the last Taiwan in the third
is called the
lunch driver
the boatman
[Music]
when the river
in equal time and that is to cross the
other side and tackle the problem game and
you have to hire this boat
the minute the second in which you arrive on the
other side is the same moment in which
the boatman also reaches statistics
and you reach it together salsa show every
time this is also a myth admins away
from Antioquia with me and you going to be
because this means that I am going to
wait for you to be at my level and we
arrive together on the net and tracen
makes sense
but it doesn't make sense
in antiquity in this poor
Phoenix minder it doesn't make sense to
wait for everyone to be at the same level and
then reach it together for it is very
difficult street because the motivation is
sweet and water and waiting court the news
of today is for you to arrive and play
we arrive together Sofia rest and of
these three types of bags
health international rees beat are very
healthy and traditionally sweet efe
borja web dilemma if I would help you
delay the illumination
Djukic and then 1912 Forest Lawn
constructive I got first and I'm going
after this swing intention is a
sweet intention you know who to be
brothers of sweaters in tradition is
considered one of the three types of
visit
which is the real
Judith First had the case first and
then you help the other people ok
the stains very violent and they have that's all we're going to
do tonight
[Music]
harder and they're going to be more tired
the replacement of the song The Spirit of
Cake just be tough from the
break a Westin goes of this mechanism I
always think to make this
Chinese monk feel Swenson and I've become
homeless one day different and he went to India
to have these teachings
by adventure and that path for 17 years
also to have these teachings
speaking of Mexico City out and
330 minutes
and I had stomach problems from
the fresh juice at the airport this is the
great suffering I had I may have
suffered a little more
Tim Anderson makes 3000
13,000 1300
just be tough
living  In very magical times and can
drive here an hour, they do
n't have to walk for 17 years,
official fighting, if they feel a little
tired,
think about who knows what, it's good,
and for errands in it,
yes, yes, thank you,
system, see you tomorrow,
excellent
in this room